We have invited into our studio professor Jeff Clark is with Arizona State University as an
anthropologist and he maintains that creationism isn't a science and therefore doesn't belong in
scientific classes. On the other hand, we have Dr. Rashad Khalifa. He is a biochemist and of course
he takes the opposite stand. And again, we're going through our phones open for your opinions about it.
It's a hot issue. It is going to be one that is you're going to be viewed with a great deal of
interest by the people in the United States in the various states and we're going to find out
how this thing is going to evolve. Well, Bob I have to make a correction here in that I will approach
the method from a scientific point of view. I agree with most of the things that Jeff
just mentioned in that science is our means to ascertain what the truth is and we have a
very powerful tool, objective and scientific tool to ascertain what events in the world are
probable and what events are not probable and this powerful tool is mathematics. Mathematics
is the most powerful, the most scientific of all of... of all the sciences and it represents the ultimate in
scientific proof. I realized that nobody can ever imagine a proof that will prove either
evolution or creation but there is something new and very exciting and I'm here to present it
to you. Well, we have... So, in... in essence, we are talking about a mathematically coded message
from outer space. You... if you read the Carl Sagan's contact, he is talking about a... novel fictitious
message from outer space. Now, this is not fiction anymore and that's why I have come here with... you're going to
have to put that in your pipe and smoke it. Yes, that's right. Yeah, that's right. So far is the particular aspect
of the Old Testament that's of issue here i.e., the book of Genesis. It's an origin myth like any other
origin there. It's not a greater nor lesser than... but you keep going back to the Genesis... the book of Genesis existence. The reason
I say that is I believe that underlies scientific creationism since it's espoused by Henry Morris.
Now, it's obvious Dr. Khalifa does not agree with Dr. Morris. Sorry, and he's not here right now. I'm debating with you. That's quite
true but who has written the texts on scientific creationism? Henry Morris and who is the founder of the Institute
for Creation Research? Henry Morris. How long ago was that? There... there... well he goes back about
20 years. Well, we're talking about now, Jeff. As soon as this program is over, I will show you irrefutable mathematical evidence that
we have a document from outer space, from the Creator telling us exactly how things... How are you gonna
prove that to the Supreme Court for heaven's sake? Absolutely, I'll prove it in any court. All right
Hold your point. We have to take some calls. This is really getting interesting. Messages
from outer space... Absolutely... to absolutely prove the creation is a fact. Yes, sir. Is it possible that
there is some sort of gigantic protoplasm somewhere out in the cosmos with all the
ingredients and all of this energy that can in fact create things? I'm not talking about an old
man enrolled with a beard and... and pearly gates and things like that. I'm talking about, is there
a possibility with our limited knowledge to envision some sort of humongous thing that thinks that can
create things? Bob, you can envision anything that you want and they have obviously not in
the strict and rigorous sense. You're not saying this about God... Oh, yes. Gods are... gods are the servants of
the societies and the cultures that create them. They have no existence apart from the societies
that... Even if it is proven to you. Well, I'd like to see somebody prove it to me. I'd you like to see it
because I can show it to you. Bob, there is no escape now that there is a super-intelligent
out there either through the theory of evolution ironically or the theory of creation.